[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hey
what is this
plastic
[Music]
and Mommy I have a cold
oops let me see here
Maddie
mad
I have not started really decorating for
the winter season and the holidays yet I
am quite behind however I did put up
some fairy lights some little beaded
snowflakes I got from a lovely friend of
ours I'm unsure about how much chaos my
cat is going to create while I'm doing
this
steps I did however bring some pine
cones in from the outdoors and I have a
lot of little bells
I think that very much sounds like the
holidays so I'm enjoying ringing Bells
while I wait to have time to decorate so
hello all you fairies and elves and
little gnomes and unicorns I suppose
whatever you are magical creature as you
can tell it is snowing outside we have
so much snow gosh it's got to be well
over two feet now so it is cold and it
is a perfect day to be indoors and to
feel all cozy as many of you know I was
taking a bit of a plan break from
YouTube and socials I just wanted to
make something very simple just to say
hello and to check in and to give you a
little update it's been a really big
year there are a lot of lovely new
friends on the channel if you haven't
introduced yourselves please introduce
yourselves down below I have to admit
I've recently done a proper job of
intimidating myself
particularly in regards to having
unrealistically high expectations in
regards to this Channel and putting a
lot of pressure on myself all of a
sudden which is um something I realized
I wanted to change I have these stories
I want to tell in my mind's eye but I
know it is unrealistic to try to execute
them especially in a short amount of
time and so I just found myself feeling
intimidated and overwhelmed and I don't
want to feel that way in regards to this
channel so I realized it was very
important to slow down my work and
address those feelings and re fall in
love with the art of visual storytelling
uploading a video and posting it you
know even just creating it suddenly
became very scary and that's why I took
a break but it was a much needed one I'm
not sure why it has suddenly felt so so
scary but perhaps it's because I've
always seen this channel as my creative
Outlet it's kind of my artist's Heart
song
and so perhaps that is why I care
so much and I put pressure on myself
approaching so much in life through the
lens of fear I think can take a lot of
that magic away I will leave you with
this little note and it is uh in regards
to a symbol that has been on this
channel from the very very beginning and
that is an acorn the acorn you have
probably seen on my wrist since the very
first video that I made many of you know
you know acorns are symbols of strength
and the wisdom that can only be acquired
through a lifetime of experiences and
learning from them but the acorn on my
wrist isn't actually meant to be a real
Acorn it is specifically an acorn button
which was a fairly well-known accessory
in clothing during a certain time it is
none other than the acorn button or
Acorn kiss involved in the scene between
Peter and Wendy in the book by J.M Berry
they share a very innocent and childlike
kiss which involves them trading some
very adorable little items and one of
them being the acorn button for me the
acorn button represents innocence and
childhood and never forgetting who you
are it is in a way and always will be a
rather childlike part of you that feels
steeply and feels a lot of those
feelings of fear even when it doesn't
really make sense if you have never read
the book Peter Pan you may not know that
it actually ends quite differently than
the movie The Lost Boys actually come
home when Wendy does and they stay in
the kind of muggle world but every time
they go to sleep in the darling's house
they start to fly in their sleep their
dreams take them back to Neverland and
so they start to fly off their beds and
so what they end up having to do to keep
the Lost Boys from just flying away they
have to tie them down to the bed so that
they can get proper sleep without
floating away to Neverland however after
several years of tying them down to the
bed and not letting them really dream of
Neverland The Lost Boys eventually stop
Flying and they grow up and they get
very normal jobs they forget in a way
all about Neverland and they don't
really fly anymore and they lose their
access to pixie dust in a way that's a
sad ending I think and when you read the
book it might surprise you how sad the
ending is however I like to think that
the author didn't really mean it that
way I think that Mr Berry wanted us all
to remember that there's a little lost
girl and Lost Boy Inside us that is
still a dreamer and that still is
excited and passionate about life as we
get older we can let a lot of worldly
emotions limit Us in living that life
but those Lost Boys could choose to
ReDiscover Neverland in a smaller way
whenever they want in the same way that
we can choose to ReDiscover our passion
and zest for life and all that magic I
felt that recently I lost a little bit
of that magic making videos and I really
want to reclaim that and find that again
and coming from Peter Pan all we have to
do is learn how to dream again and to
take courage I think of some of my
favorite quotes from movies and one of
them is of course have courage and be
kind
the other one is from a lesser-known
movie called Miss Potter we must take
courage and present ourselves to the
world and we must look upon it as an
adventure for me that Adventure is a
very quiet one it doesn't involve
traveling all over the world it doesn't
evolve doing crazy things it involves
just taking it a day at a time and
celebrating life anyway that is a long
way to share with you what I'm up to
this week it is also my birthday week I
am turning 26 on December 5th it is
crazy the year has gone by so fast it
has been an enormous year I was talking
with that to a counselor earlier this
week as I was sorting through some
emotions she asked me to summarize the
year and all I could think of was it's
been a big one so and when I'm ready to
do so which will be soon you know I will
be back to making more stories and
Whimsical fairy tales here and have
connected me with so many of you other
kinder good spirits that also love
looking at life this way sending you so
much love and hugs and Daydreams and
pixie dust and I will see you very soon
and take care goodbye